<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dana Loans</string>
    <string name="next">continue</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions"><u>Terms and Conditions</u></string>
    <string name="welcome_to_fuliza_branch">Welcome to Dana Loans</string>
    <string name="icon">icon</string>
    <string name="agree_to_privacy_policy">privacy policy</string>
    <string name="gfastloan">Get fast loan instantly. Loans are disbursed within 24-72 hours.
        After approval your loan will be disbursed to your registered Mpesa account</string>
    <string name="apr_calculations">APR Calculations</string>
    <string name="continue_application">Continue application</string>
    <string name="apr">Loan amount range from Ksh 500 - Ksh 25,000. Tenor range from 90 days(3 months) to six months. 12.5% interest is charged with no facilitation or service fees.
    We will never ask for other hidden charges. To visualize this if you borrow 5,000 for repayment period of one year with 12.5% interest rate the total interest rate
    will be 5,000 * 12.5 = 625 Ksh. Effective APR will be 47.2% - 125.2%.</string>
    <string name="enter_your_phone_number">enter your phone number</string>
    <string name="enter_your_password">enter your password</string>
    <string name="enter_phone_and_password_to_login">Enter details to login</string>
    <string name="applied_check_status">Applied? Check status.</string>
    <string name="request_loan">Request Loan</string>
    <string name="primary_phone_number">Primary Phone Number</string>
    <string name="fuliza_branch_mobile_loans">Dana Branch - Mobile Loans</string>
    <string name="enter_amount_to_apply">Enter amount to apply</string>
    <string name="thankyou_success">Thank you for allowing us to help you with your financial needs.
        We are committed to serve our customers in adherence to the prescribed codes of conducts
        and accounting profession. We are pleased to have you on-board and are eager and ready to serve you at our level best.</string>
    <string name="you_qualify">You qualify for a loan up to 5000 /=.
        Continue borrowing with us and repaying your loan to improve your credit score.
        The loan limit are set using your credit score arrived from credit bureau CRB.
        Several factors affect your credibility which include your suitability based on money transactions
        and reliability from previous transactions.</string>
    <string name="not_applied">Thank you for your interest in our services.
        You currently do not have an active loan. From our record you have not applied for a loan with us.
        To apply for a loan go back to the application page and enter the amount you wish to apply.
        We will review your application and disburse the amount when your application has been approved.
        Thank you.</string>
    <string name="applied_already">Your loan application is being reviewed.
        Please wait patiently as we review your application.
        You will get a confirmation message to update you on the status of your request.</string>
    <string name="application_success">We have received your loan application.After review and approval we
        will disburse the amount to your registered phone number  that is number you used to register to this service.
        We will take not more than 24–72hrs to complete the approval process.
        Wait patiently as we review your loan application. Check your loan status regularly to keep track of the progress.
        Any application rejection will be accompanied with a reason. </string>
    <string name="privacy_url">https://danaloanq.blogspot.com/</string>

    <string name="rate_us">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>

    <string name="banner">836756757081990_836757520415247</string>
    <string name="interstitial">836756757081990_836758863748446</string>
    <string name="nativeAd">836756757081990_836760087081657</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">https://danaloanq.blogspot.com/</string>
</resources>